dilbole.com 2016-02-05

# Dilbole.com - Privacy policy | Social Shopping India

**Dilbole (the "Site") is a web site owned by Scrapehere technologies Pvt Ltd, Bangalore, India, registered company. By using the Site, you expressly acknowledge and agree that any use of the Site will be in accordance with these Terms of Use. If you do not agree to be bound by these Terms of Use, you may not use the Site. Scrapehere may change, add or remove portions of this Agreement at any time. Each time you use the Site, the current version of this Agreement will apply**

The contents of the Site are offered for your private, non-commercial and information and discussion purposes only. All materials published by the Site (including, but not limited to prices, photographs, specifications, reviews, ratings, also known as the "Content") are protected by copyright, and owned or controlled by the Site or the party credited as the provider of the Content. If you believe that material located on or linked to by the site violates your copyright, you are encouraged to notify Scrapehere (via the contact us page) in accordance with Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") Policy. Scrapehere will respond to all such notices, including as required or appropriate by removing the infringing material or disabling all links to the infringing material.

**What information do we collect?**

a. We collect information when you register to join Dilbole by logging into an account that you already have with certain third-party social networking sites (Facebook and Twitter) via our Service. If you are not currently registered as a User on the Service and you click on "Sign in Using Facebook/Twitter", you will first be asked to enter your Facebook/Twitter credentials and then be given the option to register and join www.dilbole.com  
b. We also collect information from you when you register on our site by entering your personal details   
c. We also collect other information that you provide as part of registration, the operation, and personalization of your boards on Dilbole that cannot reasonably be used to identify or contact you.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

a. To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
b. To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

**How do we protect your information?**

a. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.   
b. Passwords you enter are salted with some random string and stored in our database. We have no power to decrypt them 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes  
Cookies are small text files that reside on a user's computer and identify you as a unique user. We use cookies to refine our site and simplify the user experience. For example, the use of cookies allows registered users to enter our site without explicitly typing in their email address and password every time. You should be aware that scrapehere.com cannot control the use of cookies by advertisers or any information advertisers may gather from their use of cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

**Third party links**

Certain links on the Site lead to resources located on servers maintained by third parties, which are independent from Scrapehere, over whom the Site has no control or connection. The Site accepts no responsibility or liability for the authenticity, availability, suitability, reliability, accuracy of the information for any damage, loss or harm, direct or consequential or any violation of local or international laws that may be incurred by your visit and/or transaction(s) on these site(s). This Agreement does not transfer from Scrapehere to you any Scrapehere or third party intellectual property, and all right, title and interest in and to such property will remain (as between the parties) solely with Scrapehere. Scrapehere does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on these third party websites. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at 'Terms Of Use'

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email:contactus@scrapehere.com 

### Dilbole.com is Social shopping app to " Showcase your style. Discover people, products and brands in one place "

Dilbole is a product bookmarking tool to showcase and discover style. It is the social shopping tool for window shoppers and brand enthusiasts. Stay stylishly up-to-date with the latest trends and smart buys whether it is fashion, jewellery, shoes, bags, home decor, furniture, electronics, stationary or home needs. We guarantee loads of fun, fashion and style for you at Dilbole.

We offer best of social shopping at one place. 

**1\. Save what you love:** Save products you love from online stores. You can collect products from over 10,000 online shopping sites including Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Asos, Jabong, Myntra, Xarato, Koovs, Limeroad, Fashionara, FabFurnish, OyeKitchen and other sites with an URL or with our [Chrome Extension](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/dil-button-dilbolecom/fkecpbhfmpbiinfainppeclfaoioplho). Your style statement can be made up of Fashion, home and other products. You can also save product using this product url tool.

**2\. Collect your products in one place:** Collect and organize your products into collections. These collections can vary from 'Things I love to buy' to 'Crazy Design Ideas for my wedding dress' and from 'Nike Shoe List' to 'My birthday wishlist'. There is no limit to the number of products you like or collect. We go with the 'Collect 'em all' attitude!!

**3\. Discover people, products and brands:** This is the right place to discover people, products and brands based on the style you are looking for. Fashion bloggers, stylists, fashionistas and proud shopaholics are part of our core. We have an ever-increasing database of 1,80,000+ added by people and online stores and over 10,000 brands. To discover people, products and brands, this is the right place to come!
